I don't call it over the record.
It's meeting in my city council for Tuesday, February 4th, 2020, 5th.
I'll begin by.
Let's get the first one.
First is we have none.
Three kinds list.
Option.
Second.
High.
Estep.
Jones.
High.
Parker.
Five.
Four minutes from the January 21st, 2020.
Four records.
Go to the meeting.
Take.
So.
High.
Five.
Budget amendment.
Number 25.
Dashed.
15.
So this amendment.
That's three things.
It allows the police department to.
Receiving an expend of $1,000 donation from Walmart.
To purchase individual first aid kits.
It moves a portion of the U.S.
A grant.
Two.
This U.S.
And though that amount is based on what.
In this U.S.
Purchased for the grant.
It's the reimbursement part.
And it also allows annual control to just.
Receive an expend.
A $30,000.
Nesley.
Curina.
Charitable trust grant.
Along with 7,000.
8 or $47,000 donation.
To.
Insult.
Fintings.
Craig.
The.
Mayor.
Council.
They will be here at the next meeting.
If I don't open everything on that.
Donation.
So.
This is a year.
For the folks that ask me about all the time.
It doesn't be $37,000.
$8,000.
$7,000.
The.
Madam.
She has already said that.
Uncle,
her letter said.
Oh,
my name.
To.
OF the same.
Oh,
Okay.
Give me.
I've got a statement,
says it.
7. Both fiber agreement with Oklahoma.
Department of Libraries agreement to receive internet services by the library paid
for by E-Rate all throughout the city manager's time.
Question of room.
Second.
Jones.
Hi.
E-step.
Barnes.
I have a question.
I want to know what to do.
Yeah.
I don't.
Hi.
Parker.
Hey.
Resume the award at least purchase agreement C-24, that's one of one of the great
months, by July.
For a $20, $23, 50, $500.
Half-ton, crude, crude cab, police vehicle with a mercy up at some differences in metropolitan
debris.
Second.
Hi.
E-step.
Jones.
Aye.
Fifth.
Ninth.
This is the same leaf smller at award-leash purchase agreement.
C-24, that's one of one A, the first on advice for the $20, $20,000.
around 1500 have done truck crew at police vehicle with mercy up it
at a related signing and payment authority to the city manager he is
does it think this is strange from the first national base at
4.7 we recognize setting up at least and by the way it's a difference of 494
we may say something real fast we are also in the future these trucks are not
out fit with cameras so we are going to be leasing cameras in the future to
go on these two trucks and then the truck two trucks that were purchased last year as
well if budget allows so in a future agenda we will see at least for cameras
because I think it's good for as many cars and trucks as we have
That's not part of the emergency, that's it that doesn't come with cameras, that's not on the emergency.
But future can be right.
Absolutely.
Good motion to approve.
Well second.
Dokel.
Aye.
Joe's.
Ten percent awarded least purchase degree in the C-2024.
One, two.
With bank of brand light, the 2020-3.5.500.
Half-time chart could get a police vehicle with mercy of a bit.
The same thing, just no chart.
We'll break a minute to withstand a number of some of the most poorly written contracts that
I don't believe they would be able to send you best interest.
From brand light, from brand light.
Essentially, they want you to pay for a vehicle that's in there.
Motion to approve.
Thank you.
Aye.
We'll have an award-leaf person.
We're going to see 24-102A.
First time.
Thank you.
The 23-dogs.
We're going to have to untrue the group cap.
Police vehicle with mercy up it.
Get it related to signing and payment authority to the city manager.
It's better to be.
It's.
It's roughly.
Fifteen dollars.
One.
Joe.
Aye.
The mayor's nominated appoint H temperors to the magma.
The Library board.
Congress by 2, 4, 26.
Motion to approve.
Sight.
Be too close.
Be set.
assessment.
A minute.
I'll pause.
It's fine.
Yes.
13.
There's a new business.
As opposed to this agenda.
14.
Staff reports.
15.
mayor council committee.
Announcements.
We've got.
February 13th, B. My name is Alan Fines, the senior center. You can be dance with all ages.
When your kids are going to have fun, there's DJ.
Watching tacos, chillies, so to this.
All the fine dining and set a great time from 6 to 9 pm.
Just before that.
and be sit the shop of a down main street tea and that's boozy and crazy. So you cruise the
different shops and you shop and you drink a little bit of the beverages, summer, Dr. Pepper.
Is that coming? Yeah. Some are different than others. And stop by the sit the shop first
you're going to have a great time with the dance. Guaranteed. Guaranteed your time. And if you need
a ride you all are. Let's see. Let's let you have that.
Right. No.
Okay. 16. So you made your communications.
I'm just a, oh, everybody sees the action we have down town. We've got the first building.
Almost all the way. The old dental office. And then we'll start with the next building.
Right after that. Was there anybody in there?
No, we actually had a few things to do with it.
Yeah. But I heard we're getting a Costco's there.
Seven jazzed.
Set in jazzed.
That's all I have.
17 adjournment.